Finding Aid for the Christopher Coover Collection of Theater Broadsides, 1790-1868
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- England, 1790-1862, II.; Item 3-Item 17
  - London, 1814-1862, II. A; Item 3-Item 16
    - Sadler's Wells Theatre, 1844-1862, 2. A. 2; Item 7-Item 15
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 11 August 1844, 1 broadside ([2] pages); 39 x 26 cm.; Presumably the first playbill for Sadler's Wells under the management of Samuel Phelps and Mary Warner. (Box 1, Item 07)
        Knowles, James Sheridan, 1784-1862: Bridal
        Massinger, Philip, 1583-1640: City madam
        Morton, John Maddison, 1811-1891: Thumping legacy
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: Hamlet
        Stirling, Edward, 1807-1894: Bachelor's buttons
        Wilks, Thomas Egerton, 1812-1854: Captain's not a-miss
        Mr. G. Bennett( Bennett, G. J. (George John), 1800-1879)
        Miss Cooper ( Cooper, Fanny, 1814-1872)
        Mr. Coreno ( Coreno, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Evain ( Evain, W. H., Mr., fl. 1850)
        S. G. Fairbrother and Son ( Fairbrother, S. G. (Samuel Glover), fl. 1823-1855)
        Mr. Forman ( Forman, George Frederick, 1811-1852)
        Mr. Francis ( Francis, Mr., 19th cent.)
        [Mr.] Franks ( Franks, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Thomas Longden Greenwood ( Greenwood, T. L. (Thomas Longdon), 1806-1879)
        Miss Kate Howard ( Howard, Kate, 19th cent.)
        Miss Huddart ( Huddart, Fanny, d. 1880)
        Mr. Knight ( Knight, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Lebatt ( Lebatt, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss G. Lebatt ( Lebatt, G., Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss Morel ( Morel, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mr. Morton ( Morton, Mr., 19th cent. )
        Mr. Sharpe ( Sharpe, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mrs. Warner ( Warner, Mary Amelia, 1804-1854)
        Mr. Williams ( Williams, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. A. Younge ( Younge, A.)
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 6 September 1844, 1 broadside; 51 x 26 cm. (Box 1, Item 08)
        Reduced title transcription: Theatre Royal, Sadler’s Wells: Lessee, Thomas Longden Greenwood … Under the management of Mrs. Warner and Mr. Phelps ... Friday, September 6, 1844, and Saturday, 7th, the performances will commence with Sheridan Knowles’s play of The Hunchback ... after which, the popular farce of The Nervous Man ... to conclude with the laughable farce called The Railroad Station ... On Monday and Tuesday .., the tragedy of The Bridal, On Wednesday and Thursday, Sheridan’s comedy of The Rivals, On Friday and Saturday … Shakspere’s tragedy of Hamlet … in preparation, Shakspere’s tragedy of King John ... S. G. Fairbrother and Son, Printers, 31, Bow Street Covent Garden.
        Bernard, William Bayle, 1807-1875: Nervous man
        Knowles, James Sheridan, 1784-1862: Hunchback
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: King John
        Sheridan, Richard Brinsley, 1751-1816: Rivals
        Wilks, Thomas Egerton, 1812-1854: Railroad station
        Mr. Coreno ( Coreno, Mr.)
        Mr. C. Fenton ( Fenton, Charles, d. 1877)
        Mr. Franks ( Franks, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Graham ( Graham, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Green ( Green, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Henry Marston ( Marston, Henry, 1804-1883)
        Mr. W. Montgomery ( Montgomery, W. H. (William Henry), 1810-1886)
        Mr. Morelli ( Morelli, Charles Francis, 1800-1882)
        Miss Morelli (possibly Morelli, Olivia Elizabeth, b. 1828)
        Mr. Morton ( Morton, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Sievier ( Sievier, Mr.)
        Miss Thornbury ( Thornbury, Miss, 19th cent.)
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 26-29 August [1846], 1 broadside; 49 x 26 cm. (Box 1, Item 09)
        Reduced title transcription: Theatre Royal, Sadler’s Wells: Lessees. Messrs. Greenwood and Phelps, under the management of Mr. Phelps, Wednesday, Aug. 26, Thursday, 27, Friday, 28, & Saturday 29, will be produced … Westland Marston’s play of The Patrician’s daughter … to be followed by an interlude by Charles Selby entitled A Lady & gentleman in a peculiarly perplexing predicament … To conclude with the farce entitled Manoeuvring ... Henry IVth will be repeated twice next week: Shakspere’s tragedy of Romeo and Juliet ... will be speedily produced: Sergeant Talfourd's tragedy of Ion is also in a forward state of rehearsal ... S. G. Fairbrother, Printer, 31 Bow Street, Covent Garden.
        Edgeworth, Maria, 1767-1849: Manoeuvring
        Marston, Westland, 1819-1890: Patrician's daughter
        Selby, Charles, 1802?-1863: Lady and gentleman in a peculiarly perplexing predicament
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: King Henry IV
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: Romeo and Juliet
        Miss Laura Addison ( Addison, Laura, 1822-1852)
        Mr. Branson ( Branson, William Scholes, d. 1884)
        Mrs. Brougham ( Brougham, John, Mrs.)
        S. G. Fairbrother, printer ( Fairbrother, S. G. (Samuel Glover), fl. 1823-1855)
        Mrs. Frances ( Frances, Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Mrs. Francis ( Francis, Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Mrs. Graham ( Graham, Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Mr. T. L. Greenwood ( Greenwood, T. L. (Thomas Longdon), 1806-1879)
        Mr. Hoskins ( Hoskins, William, 1815 or 16-1886)
        Mr. Mellon ( Mellon, Henry, 1808-1876)
        Mrs. Leigh Murray ( Murray, Elizabeth Leigh, 1815-1892 )
        Mr. Scharf (there is also a Mr. Scharfe, likely the same person) ( Scharf, Henry, 1822-1887 )
        Mr. Scoley ( Scoley, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Stephens ( Stephens, Miss, 19th cent. )
        Mr. Stilt ( Stilt, Charles, d. 1851)
        Mr. Wilkins ( Wilkins, John, 19th cent.)
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 22 September 1849, 1 broadside; 51 x 25 cm. (Box 1, Item 10)
        Reduced title transcription: Theatre Royal, Sadler’s Wells: Lessees, Messrs. Greenwood and Phelps, under the management of Mr. Phelps, this evening, Friday, Sept. 21st, there will be no performance, in consequence of the Churchwardens of the Parish having appointed the day as one of humiliation and prayer: To-morrow, Saturday, Sept. 22nd, 1849, will be presented … Colley Cibber's comedy of She Would and She Would Not ... to be followed by the petite comedy, in two acts, of A Day After the Wedding ... to conclude with … a new farce by J. Wooler, entitled Plots for Petticoats: Shakspere’s play of Measure for Measure will be repeated on Monday and Tuesday: Shakspere’s play of The Tempest will be performed on Wednesday and Thursday: The Merchant of Venice will be repeated in a few days: the production of Shakspere’s tragedy of Antony & Cleopatra ... is unavoidably postponed until October … S. G. Fairbrother, Printer, 31, Bow Street, Covent Garden.
        Cibber, Colley, 1671-1757: She would and she would not
        Kemble, Marie Thérèse, 1774-1838: Day after the wedding
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: Antony and Cleopatra
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: Measure for measure
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: Tempest
        Wooler, J. P. (John Pratt), 1824-1868: Plots for petticoats
        Miss T. Bassano ( Bassano, T., Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss Carlstein ( Carlstein, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mr. Clinton ( Clinton, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. G. K. Dickinson ( Dickinson, G. K., d. 1863)
        Mr. Dolman ( Dolman, John, 1824-1895)
        Miss Fitzpatrick ( Fitzpatrick, Helen, 19th cent.)
        Mr. W. H. Montgomery ( Montgomery, W. H. (William Henry), 1810-1886)
        Miss Julia St. George ( St. George, Julia, 1822 or 3-1903)
        Mrs. G. Smith ( Smith, G., Mrs., 19th cent.)
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 30 April 1850, 1 broadside; 51 x 26 cm. (Box 1, Item 11)
        Reduced title transcription: Theatre Royal, Sadler’s Wells: Lessees, Messrs. Greenwood and Phelps, under the management of Mr. Phelps: for the benefit of Mr. G. Bennett on which occasion Miss Jane Bennett will make her first appearance: On Tuesday, April 30th, 1850, the performances will commence with the new play in five acts, by Mr. G. Bennett, entitled Retribution … After which, Sheridan’s celebrated comedy of The Rivals ... S. G. Fairbrother, Printer, 31, Bow Street, Covent Garden.
        Bennett, G. J. (George John), 1800-1879: Retribution
        Mr. George Bennett ( Bennett, G. J. (George John), 1800-1879)
        Miss Jane Bennett ( Bennett, Jane, b. 1832)
        Mrs. Brougham ( Brougham, John, Mrs. )
        Miss A. Brown ( Brown, A., Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss Johnstone ( Johnstone, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss Morelli ( Morelli, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mr. Henry Nye ( Nye, Henry, fl. 1849)
        Master Righton ( Righton, Thomas Edward Corrie Burns, 1838-1899)
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 2 March [1854], 1 broadside; 51 x 26 cm.; A second copy is included. March 2 was on a Thursday in 1854 according to perpetual calendar. Phelps did not start at Sadler’s Wells until 1844. (Box 1, Item 12)
        Reduced title transcription: Theatre Royal, Sadler’s Wells: Lessees, Messrs Greenwood and Phelps: Mr. Phelps respectfully announces his Benefit Night for Thursday, March 2nd, when will be revived Fielding's Play, in Three Acts, of The Miser ... To conclude with the comedy of Wild Oats ... S. G. Fairbrother, Printer, 31, Bow Street, Covent Garden.
        Fielding, Henry, 1707-1754: Miser
        O'Keeffe, John, 1747-1833: Wild oats
        Mr. Lewis Ball ( Ball, Lewis, 1820-1905)
        Mr. Barrett ( Barrett, Henry Michael, d. 1872)
        Mr. Frost ( Frost, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Greenwood ( Greenwood, T. L. (Thomas Longdon), 1806-1879)
        Miss Katharine Hickson ( Hickson, Katharine)
        Mr. Josephs ( Josephs, Mr., 19th cent. )
        Mr. Lacy ( Lacy, Walter, 1809-1898)
        Mr. Lloyd ( Lloyd, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Lunt ( Lunt, James, d. 1879)
        Mr. Meagreson ( Meagreson, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. C. Mortimer ( Mortimer, C., Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. J. W. Ray ( Ray, J. W. (John William), d. 1871)
        Mr. Rousby ( Rousby, Wybert (William Wybert))
        Mr. Scholey ( Scholey, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mrs. Ternan ( Ternan, Mrs. (Thomas), 1802-1873)
        Miss Eliza Travers ( Travers, Eliza)
        Miss Wyatt ( Wyatt, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss F. Younge ( Younge, F., Miss, 19th cent.)
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 17 November 1859, 1 broadside; 51 x 25 cm. (Box 1, Item 13)
        Reduced title transcription: Theatre Royal, Sadler’s Wells: Lessees, Messrs. Greenwood and Phelps, under the management of Mr. Phelps: This evening, Thursday, Nov. 17, 1859 and Friday, November 18th, the performances will commence with Sheridan Knowles’ comedy of The Love Chase ... To conclude with Charles Dance's comedy, in two acts, entitled Sons & Systems ... On Saturday … Shakespeare’s tragedy of Macbeth ... In consequence of the continued attraction on the performance of The Fool's Revenge, it will be repeated on Thursday and Friday next … Henry Pownceby, Steam Machine Printer, 43, Leman Street, Whitechapel
        Dance, Charles, 1794-1863: Sons and systems
        Knowles, James Sheridan, 1784-1862: Love chase
        Taylor, Tom, 1817-1880: Fool’s revenge
        Mr. Chapman ( Chapman, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Gray ( Gray, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mr. Greenwood ( Greenwood, T. L. (Thomas Longdon), 1806-1879 )
        Mr. T. C. Harris ( Harris, T. C., Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Hart ( Hart, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss Heath ( Barrett, Caroline, 1835-1887)
        Miss R. Herbert ( Herbert, R., Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mrs. J. B. Hill ( Hill, J. B., Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Lickfold ( Lickfold, James, d. 1888)
        Miss Caroline Parkes ( Parkes, Caroline, 1838-1877)
        Mr. Paxon ( Paxon, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Poole ( Poole, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Henry Pownceby, printer ( Pownceby, Henry)
        Mr. Frederick Robinson ( Robinson, Frederic, 1832-1912)
        Mr. C. Seyton ( Seyton, Charles, d. 1894)
        Mr. Warde ( Warde, Mr., 19th cent.)
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 17 August 1861, 1 broadside; 51 x 26 cm. (Box 1, Item 14)
        Reduced title transcription: Theatre Royal, Sadler’s Wells: Sole lessee, Mr. Phelps: last night of performance … The public is respectfully informed that a performance will take place at this theatre, on Saturday, August 17th, 1861, for the benefit of an artist, suffering from severe illness, Mr. Phelps, … has most liberally granted the use of the theatre, free of charge, and his son, Mr. Edmund Phelps, has kindly consented to sustain two characters … The entertainments will commence at a Quarter to seven, with four scenes from Sheridan Knowles' Play of The Hunchback ... A song, by Miss Fanny Josephs, To be followed by three scenes from The Love Chase ... In the course of the Evening, Mrs Stirling will deliver an address, written by Tom Taylor, Esq. to be followed by a selection of scenes from Shakespeare’s comedy of As You Like It ... After which, the trial scene, from Shakespeare’s play of The Merchant of Venice ... In the course of the evening, Miss Caroline Parkes will give her new entertainment song, entitled The Delights of the dance, After which two scenes from Sheridan’s comedy of The School for Scandal ... The whole to conclude with Buckstone’s favorite farce, entitled A Kiss in the dark … Pownceby, Steam Printer, 43, Leman Street, Whitechapel.
        Buckstone, John Baldwin, 1802-1879: Kiss in the dark
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: As you like it
        Miss Atkinson ( Atkinson, Emma)
        Mr. H. S. Carleton ( Carleton, H. S., Mr.)
        Mr. Davis ( Davis, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Alice Evans ( Evans, Alice, 19th cent.)
        Mrs. Hill ( Hill, J. B., Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Miss Hill ( Hill, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss Johnson ( Johnson, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Miss Fanny Josephs ( Josephs, Fanny, d. 1890)
        Miss Lavine ( Lavine, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mr. F. Morton ( Morton, F., Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Oliver ( Oliver, Martha Cranmer, 1834-1880)
        Mr. Edmund Phelps ( Phelps, Edmund, 1838-1870)
        Mr. Pigeon ( Pigeon, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Henry Pownceby, printer ( Pownceby, Henry )
        Mr. Alfred Rayner ( Rayner, Alfred, d. 1898)
        Mrs. St. Henry ( St. Henry, Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Mrs. Stirling ( Stirling, Fanny, 1815-1895)
        Mr. W. H. Swanborough ( Swanborough, W. H. (William Henry), ca. 1830-1886)
        Tom Taylor ( Taylor, Tom, 1817-1880)
        Mr. Webster Vernon ( Vernon, W. H., 1834-1905)
        Mr. Herman Vezin ( Vezin, Hermann, 1829-1910)
      - Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England) 25 October [1862], 1 broadside; 51 x 26 cm.; Phelps resigned from Sadler’s Wells earlier in 1862 but returned for some shows. The perpetual calendar shows that October 25th was a Saturday in 1862 and the play, A Chinese romance, by Horne, was licensed in January 1862 for performance at the New Royalty Theatre. (Box 1, Item 15)
        Reduced title transcription: Theatre Royal, Sadler’s Wells: Under the management of Miss Catherine Lucette: Mr. Phelps every evening, for a limited number of nights … On Saturday, Oct. 25th, & Monday and Tuesday following, the performances will commence with Shakspeare’s tragedy, in five acts, of Othello, The Moor of Venice … Characteristic pas seul by Miss Rosa Nathan: To conclude with … a new comic drama, written by the author of Two heads are better than one, entitled Chinese romance … On Wednesday, Oct. 29th, Shakspeare’s play of The Merchant of Venice … Mr. Phelps’ farewell benefit, and last performance but one at this theatre, on Thursday evening, Nov. 6th … “Nassau Steam Press,” W. S. Johnson & Co., 60, St. Martin’s Lane, W. C.
        Horne, F. Lennox: Chinese romance
        Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616: Othello
        Miss Clements ( Clements, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mr. C. Crook ( Crook, C., Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Emily Dowton ( Dowton, Emily)
        Mrs. Dowton ( Dowton, Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Mr. E. F. Edgar ( Edgar, Edward Fisher, d. 1884)
        Mr. Fisher( Fisher, David, 1816-1887)
        Mr. Henry Forrester ( Forrester, Henry, 1827-1882)
        Mr. Horton ( Horton, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. James Johnstone ( Johnstone, James, b. 1817)
        Mr. C. Lloyds ( Lloyds, C., Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Catherine Lucette ( Lucette, Catherine, d. 1892)
        Miss Sophie Miles ( Miles, Sophie, d. 1891)
        Mr. A. Montague ( Montague, A., Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Mowbray ( Mowbray, Thomas, 1822-1900)
        Miss Rosa Nathan ( Nathan, Rosa)
        Mr. Northcote ( Northcote, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Regan ( Regan, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Richards ( Richards, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Escott Shelley ( Shelley, Escott)
        Mr. John St. Luke ( St. Luke, John, 19th cent.)
        Mr. Willson ( Willson, Mr., 19th cent.)
        “Nassau Steam Press,” W. S. Johnson & Co. ( W.S. Johnson and Co. (London, England) )
    - Saint James' Theatre, 1837, 2. A. 3; Item 16
      - Saint James' Theatre (London, England), 29 December 1837, 1 broadside; 35 x 21 cm. (Box 1, Item 16)
        Reduced title transcription: Pascal Bruno, founded on Mr. Hook’s novel, having been received most enthusiastically throughout, will be repeated every evening: Theatre Royal St. James's: This evening, Friday, December 29, 1837 will be performed a popular burletta, founded on and called Guy Mannering … After which, the famous burletta written by Boz. entitled Is She His Wife? Or, Something Singular! ... To conclude with … an entirely new romantic burletta, in two acts, called Pascal Bruno, adapted from Mr. Theodore Hook's translation of the celebrated tale by Mons. Alexandre Dumas … The Incidental music selected and composed by Mr. G. F. Stansbury, the dances arranged by Mrs. Wells, the scenery by Mr. Nicholls ... In the course of the piece, Mr. Wright and Madame Sala will dance their celebrated burlesque of The Cuchacha
        Bishop, Henry R. (Henry Rowley), Sir, 1786-1855: Guy Mannering
        Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870: Is she his wife?, or, Something singular
        Dumas, Alexandre, 1802-1870: Pascal Bruno
        Cachucha
        Mr. Alexander ( Alexander, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Miss Allison (later Mrs. Seymour) ( Allison, Miss, b. 1816)
        Miss C. Booth ( Booth, C., Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mr. Brookes ( Brookes, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Burnet ( Burnet, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Gardner (possibly John Gardiner, d. 1851) ( Gardner, Mr., 19th cent. )
        Mr. A. Giubilei (also spelled Guibilei on playbill - Giubilei, A., Mr.)
        Mr. H. Hall ( Hall, Henry, 1804-1858)
        Mr. Harley ( Harley, John Pritt, 1786-1858)
        Mr. Hart ( Hart, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Hollingsworth ( Hollingsworth, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Theodore Hook ( Hook, Theodore Edward, 1788-1841)
        Mr. Moore ( Moore, Mr., 19th cent.)
        Mrs. Penson ( Penson, Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Miss Rainforth ( Rainforth, Elizabeth, 1814-1877)
        Madame Sala ( Sala, Madame, 1792-1860)
        Mr. Sidney ( Sidney, Mr., 19th cent. )
        Miss Julia Smith ( Smith, Julia, 19th cent.)
        Miss Smith ( Smith, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mr. G. F. Stansbury ( Stansbury, George Frederick, 1800-1845 )
        Miss Stuart ( Stuart, Miss, 19th cent.)
        Mrs. Wells ( Wells, Mrs., 19th cent.)
        Mr. Wright ( Wright, Edward Richard, 1813-1859)
  - York, 1790, II. B; Item 17
    - Theatre Royal (York, England), 13 April 1790, 1 broadside; 31 x 21 cm. (Box 1, Item 17)
      Reduced title transcription: Theatre-Royal, York: Tuesday evening, April 13, 1790, will be presented a comedy, called The Clandestine marriage ... To which will be added Mr. Sheridan's celebrated farce, called The Critic; or, A Tragedy Rehears'd ... To conclude with A Grand Naval Engagement, and Rule Brittannia, in Full Chorus …
      Colman, George, 1732-1794: Clandestine marriage
      Sheridan, Richard Brinsley, 1751-1816: Critic
      Mrs. Cummins ( Cummins, Mrs.)
      Mr. Draycott ( Draycott, Mr.)
      Mr. Fawcett ( Fawcett, Mr. (John), 1768-1837)
      Mrs. Fawcett ( Fawcett, Susan, d. 1797)
      Mrs. French ( French, Mary Amelia, d. 1887 )
      Mrs. Kennedy ( Kennedy, Agnes, ca. 1759-1832)
      Mr. Kennedy ( Kennedy, Thomas, ca. 1750-1808)
      Mr. King ( King, Thomas, 1730-1805)
      Mr. Leng ( Leng, Mr.)
      Mrs. Leng ( Leng, Mrs.)
      Mr. Michell ( Michell, Mr.)
      Mr. Penson ( Penson, George, d. 1833)
      Mr. Snagg ( Snagg, Thomas, 1746-1812)
      Mr. Southgate ( Southgate, Mr.)
      Mr. Townsend ( Townsend, Edward Evans, 1766-1809)
      Mr. Turpin ( Turpin, Mr.)
      Mr. Warren ( Warren, Mr.)
      Mr. J. Wilkinson ( Wilkinson, John Joseph Tate, 1769 or 70-1846)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Contributors
Boston Theatre (Washington Street, Boston, Mass.); Tremont Theatre (Boston, Mass.); Covent Garden Theatre; Royal Italian Opera (London, England); Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England); Saint James' Theatre (London, England); Theatre Royal (York, England)
Subjects
Phelps, Samuel, 1804-1878; Boston Theatre (Washington Street, Boston, Mass.); Tremont Theatre (Boston, Mass.); Covent Garden Theatre; Royal Italian Opera (London, England); Sadler's Wells Theatre (London, England); Saint James' Theatre (London, England); Theatre Royal (York, England); Playbills--Massachusetts--Boston--Specimens; Playbills--England--London--Specimens; Playbills--England--York--Specimens; Broadsides--Massachusetts--Boston--Specimens; Broadsides--England--London--Specimens; Broadsides--England--York--Specimens; Printed ephemera--Massachusetts--Boston--Specimens; Printed ephemera--England--London--Specimens; Printed ephemera--England--York--Specimens; Theater--Massachusetts--Boston--19th century; Theater--England--London--19th century; Theater--England--York--18th century
Genres
Broadsides; Playbills
Associated Material
Additional Guides
All playbills in the collection are cataloged in WorldCat and are available in BISON, the online catalog for the University at Buffalo Libraries, by performing a "Title begins with" search under "Christopher Coover Collection of Theatre Broadsides".
All playbills have been digitized and full text transcriptions have been prepared. The full text of these transcriptions is keyword searchable. Any personnel not stated in the container list description can be searched through the transcriptions as can the names of characters in the plays.